If the sun dies, so do we.
Sunshine is a science fiction, thriller film directed by Danny Boyle.
Fifty years into the future, the sun is dying, and Earth
is threatened by arctic temperatures.
A team of astronauts is sent to revive the Sun — but the mission fails.
Seven years later, a new team is sent to finish
the mission as mankind’s last hope.
Capa, played by Cillian Murphy.
Cassie, played by Rose Byrne.
Mace, played by Chris Evans.
Corazon, played by Michelle Yeoh.
Searle, played by Cliff Curtis.
Kaneda, played by Hiroyuki Sanada.
Sunshine is a 2007 British science fiction psychological thriller film
directed by Danny Boyle and written by Alex Garland.
Starring an ensemble cast including Rose Byrne, Cliff Curtis, Chris Evans, Troy Garity, Cillian Murphy, Hiroyuki Sanada, Benedict Wong and Michelle Yeoh,
the film takes place in 2057, where a group of astronauts aboard the Icarus II are sent on a dangerous mission to reignite the dying Sun.
Sunshine was released in the United Kingdom on 6
April 2007 by Fox Searchlight Pictures.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and
grossed $35 million against a $40M budget.
The film explores themes of space marine, saving
the world, bomb, sun, space suit.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.